Contact

razabandali@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/raza-moreaurn-bsn-ccrn-scrn-4096a7139 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Critical Care
Basic Life Support (BLS)

Raza Moreau RN, BSN, CCRN, SCRN

Registered Nurse at UCSF Medical Center

San Francisco, California

Summary

Experienced Neuro Intensive Care Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Electronic Medical Record (EMR), Nursing, Inpatient Care, Critical Care Nursing, and Advanced Cardiac Life Support.

Experience

UCSF Medical Center Neuro ICU Registered Nurse July 2017 - Present (3 years) San Francisco Bay Area

Parallon Workforce Management Solutions Critical Care Registered Nurse May 2016 - Present (4 years 2 months) Greater Denver Area

UCHealth

Critical Care RN/ Relief Charge Neuro ICU February 2015 - Present (5 years 5 months) Greater Denver Area

UCHealth

CNA

June 2008 - December 2013 (5 years 7 months)

Aurora

Education

University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus Masters, Health Informatics · (2017 - 2019)

University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2014 - 2014)

Metropolitan State University of Denver
Bachelor of Science - BS, Environmental Science · (2001 - 2005)